Okay.
Ooh-wee, I am fuming, y'all.
So I was taking my ten-year-old,
Destiny, to school this morning.
Now, she loves
that 96.5 radio station.
It's like the hits
or top 40 hits or something.
This rap song comes on.
And it was just... disgusting.
It's... You okay, baby?
Want a juice box?
So, uh, I-I looked up
the lyrics.
And the song is by this guy,
Paper Boi,
and I'm gonna read y'all
what was playing.
So there's gonna be
some cussing.
But it's not my words.
Okay, so here it goes.
"Bitch, I need reparations.
"N-Niggas tired of dancing
like The Temptations.
"Sell a dime bag
or that new crack, fentanyl.
"The same reason Prince killed.
"My dick is like a tree trunk.
"Baby, catch this tree sap.
"Kicked you out the condo.
"This ain't the place
you sleep at.
"Baby, slide on the dick.
"You can do it all night.
"You can be my baby mama.
You can't ever be my wife."
Here's where it
gets crazy, y'all.
"Said no to college
'cause it's no fun.
"Mo' drugs and mo' guns.
"But I still might have
to slap a trick.
Shout-out Colin Kaepernick."
:
I'm sorry.
It's just, like,
this is what was on.
* Uh, told a bitch
you motherfuckin' right *
* Told a bitch
you motherfuckin' right. *
Hey!
Oh, boy, I can't believe
that single went gold already.
Yo, that white woman crying,
that was the best thing that
could've happened to us, man.
Their tears are powerful.
They are. They really are.
Yo, I was gonna send her ass
a gift,
but, uh,
she was slick hatin', though.
Oh, man. Hey, y'all fellas
want another round of shots?
-Oh, hell yeah, man.
-Yeah. -Sure, man.
BARTENDER:
1800-- it's on me.
Not even gonna charge y'all
for these, all right?
-Oh, thanks, man.
-Thanks.
Matter of fact,
might take one with y'all.
-Oh, all right.
-Oh... -Hey...
White tears.
Oh, it tastes like free.
Ah.
Look, we got to talk about...
Yo. Y
Yeah, man.
Man, see, listen,
I was trying to see
if I could kick some business
with you, brother.
Like, I got a handle
on a couple...
Well, actually, you know, we're
kind of off the clock right now,
-so, like, we're just...
-Man, fuck you, dude!
I'm talking to Paper Boi.
Okey-dokey.
BARTENDER:
Anyway, man, so...
put me on.
Huh?
Put... me... on.
I'm trying to get like you,
you know.
-I need this shit.
-MAN: Order up. Let's go, now.
Yes, sir, it'll be right up.
Okay, that was... weird.
Man, that shit be happening
all the time now, man.
It's kind of cool.
You know?
'Cause people recognize you.
ALFRED:
Yeah, man, that's overrated.
Nah. I don't think it is
'cause, like,
I'm always getting stunted on.
I would love to be the person
who can stunt on somebody.
You can stunt on anybody
you want.
Hey, man, shit.
Look, welcome to Atlanta.
Man, all you need is some money.
I don't even think it's that.
I once bought a homeless person
a McDonald's meal.
He threw it away
right in front of me.
Stunted on right there.
ALFRED:
Look, trust me, man.
This town run off
stunting on people.
Them streaming checks
come in yet?
-Monday.
It's gonna be less
than you expected,
but more than I was, so...
Oh. Coolio 'cause I need
that money, yo.
I feel you.
I feel... I feel everything.
-* Where tiny men
have been absorbed... *
VAN:
Hey, babe.
EARN:
Hey. What's up?
Mm. I love how you send all
your important mail to my house.
Yeah. That's love. I trust you.
You're not gonna believe
what happened today.
What happened today?
VAN:
You know how we've been trying
to go to this Beyoncé concert?
This heifer Kristina goes out
and buys herself a VIP ticket.
* She asked me who died... *
That means
we can't sit together.
And not everybody can afford
350 extra dollars
for a fucking VIP ticket.
And she's like, "Well, maybe
I can meet all y'all afterwards.
Maybe."
She stunted on you.
She stunted on me.
Well, you know what?
This weekend...
Mm-hmm.
...we're doing it big.
I'm calling it.
-No more Mr. Nice Earn.
-Yeah, seriously.
-Okay, Diddy.
The stunters have become
the stunted.
-All right, all right.
-Yeah.
-Puff Daddy.
-Look at this.
Puff Zaddy.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
-Shit.
-Oh, my God.
-You're gonna get us robbed.
Hey, what up, boy?
-Hey! Paper Boi in the house.
-Good to see you.
-That's my boy, Darius, man.
Aw, we got a hugger, man.
Nice to meet you.
-Hey, great.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
CLARK: Yo, that's my boy, Boogz,
right there.
How y'all doing?
Squad up in here, man,
that's my right-hand man.
:
Wait a minute... Them the Tubs?
Aw, what you looking at, this?
-You must be looking at this,
man. -ALFRED: Come on, man.
Yo, Tub dubs.
My mom, she used to work
-in the government.
: What?
Yeah, she got 'em to me
before they stopped making 'em,
-so, kind of like
a little good luck charm. -Wow.
CLARK:
Yeah, man.
But, yo, we're working
on some hot tracks right now.
You trying to, you trying to hop
in a couple of tracks, man?
ALFRED:
Oh, yeah?
We could get a couple verses in.
Come on, man. We might as well.
Oh, yeah, man. Well, I got
to get in the zone first, man.
-Yep. -I got to, like,
smoke and shit. You hear me?
CLARK:
Nah, I feel you, totally, bro...
Yeah, I rolled a blunt, man.
You
CLARK:
Man, that sounds dope,
but I don't,
I don't really smoke.
-Nah, I got to keep
my voice right.
But, hey, thanks, man.
Yeah, man, I-I hear you.
All right, well, that's why
I brought this Hen, though.
-DARIUS: Yeah, boy.
You trying to get in on this,
I know, right?
Man! You brought the Hen,
that's dope!
I know you trying
to get in on this, my nigga.
Hey, that's what's up, man.
I don't really drink.
We got bottles here for y'all,
though.
But I don't really drink
like that.
-That's lit, though, man.
-Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, man, yo.
Do your thing, man.
Get in your zone. I'm about
to lay down something, dude.
Play that one.
Yo, Clark is pretty cool, man.
-Yeah.
-Nice guy.
Yeah, I know.
CLARK: Hey, yo, start it
after the chorus.
-ENGINEER: Okay, got you, bro.
-Yeah, track get me hype.
*
ALFRED :
It's dope.
Yo.
* Walk it, walk it, walk it
like a bird, bird, bird *
* Talking to the plug like *
* What's the word, word, word? *
* Swerve, swerve, swerve *
* Off the curb, curb, curb *
* Hennessy plus the herb,
plus the herb, herb, herb *
* Yo, I just bought a dinosaur
like Nicolas Cage. *
-Uh...
Hey, what happened?
Hey, what's going on?
ENGINEER:
Hey, sorry, man.
The program just crashed
or something.
CLARK:
The program just crashed?
ENGINEER: I just got to up...
we got to update, probably.
-Okay.
-ENGINEER: I'm sorry, man.
It just...
yeah, it just crashed.
Dude, don't crash it again,
dude.
ENGINEER:
Yeah, that's my bad.
-CLARK: Yeah, it's your bad.
-It just crashed, so...
Dude, if it crashes again,
I'm gonna crash my foot
in your ass.
Fix that shit, okay?
ENGINEER: Yeah, that's-that's
my bad. You know...
Hey, yo, Al, man.
You fucks with that, man?
-Dude, that was...
-That shit was dope to me, man.
Boy, you're
a strapping young lad.
-It's good, man. -CLARK: Hey,
man. I appreciate you, Darius.
You got that, man.
Yo, it's the gift, bro.
Like, I was just freestyling
off the top, right?
And then I just got
into this different world, man.
I don't even remember
what I said, to be real, man.
I felt that, man.
Hopefully, I can
recreate it, you know,
um, after I listen to it because
the engineer did his job.
He recorded it, right?
Yeah, we got that.
I'm just double-checking
-Right, right.
-Yo.
-You need to stop playing, dawg.
Okay? -Man, I'm not...
-I'm not playing. It's...
-Hey, yo, Boogz, it's cool, man.
'Cause it's all love, right?
Hey, man, I love you, bro.
I wouldn't hurt you.
I'd never put a hand on you.
ENGINEER:
I know that.
Just don't fuck up
because I'm not the only one
with hands in this world.
You know what I'm saying?
ENGINEER: Yeah, man.
I love you, too.
-Let's do this.
-Yeah, hey, stop talking.
Damn, this place
is kind of nice.
Yeah, and it serves alcohol.
'Cause, you know,
when you're drunk,
the one thing you want to do
is sit in a chair for two hours.
-Yeah, totally.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, uh, can I get, uh,
two tickets
for Fast and Furious?
Oh, regular or VIP?
-It doesn't matter. Two VIPs.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
I'm sorry,
but I can't take
a bill that large.
It's all right, um...
just use my debit.
Mm-hmm. Uh, can I see an ID
or a driver's license?
Thank you.
Okay. I got to make a copy
of these every time we swipe it,
so, um, are you good on tickets?
You got to make a copy
every time you swipe?
Yeah, I know it's crazy.
It's a new policy, though.
Yeah, but...
Yeah, I don't want a bunch
of copies of my debit card
and my driver's license
all around, you know?
What if somebody steals it?
-We're not responsible for that.
It's fine, 'cause I have cash.
I could just pay with it.
No, it's fine.
Um, it's okay, we'll...
We'll figure something else out.
It's fine. Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
Babe, it's fine. I can pay.
No, it... This place feels weird
to you, right?
-It feels kind of strange.
-Yeah. It's a weird policy.
Yeah, yeah. And when did they
even start doing that?
$32.28.
What?
That's a hund...
Hold on right there.
Excuse me, sir.
I-I know you don't know me,
but I just tried to pay
with a hundred, and they told...
Wow. Okay, let's-let's get out
of here. Yeah.
Thanks very much.
* Gray love *
* Hungover Sunday love *
* Come over, no, stay, love... *
I told you not to use
the $100 bill.
Why? It's legal U.S. tender.
Nobody uses cash
like that anymore.
What are you, Gucci Mane?
Come on.
I should be able to use
a $100 bill, okay?
What happened to us was racist.
-It was weird.
-No, it was racism.
-Textbook.
I caught that lady red-handed.
-You can't say that.
Red-handed. Like, red skin.
Like, Native Americans
'cause they're always stealing.
I didn't even know.
I didn't even know that.
-I... Damn.
* Come over, no, stay, love... *
You're fucking with me.
That's not funny.
-That's not funny.
-It's funny.
-No.
It sounds real.
I don't think that's where
it comes from.
Oh, my God.
Hey, man.
I see you out here getting that
endorsement money.
-I need some of that shit.
-Hell yeah.
That Yoo-hoo commercial.
-That shit fire, boy. "Yoo-hoo!"
Thanks, man.
The commercials
pay really well, too.
You got to get on that,
Paper Boi.
Man, I don't know, man.
I ain't got the image
for that shit like you do.
What you mean
They got him for the, uh,
what's that, the rap snack?
Rap Snacks.
-Aw, man.
-Yeah, man.
-That-That's dope.
Yeah, man, they wanted
to give me my own flavor called
-Cocaine White Cheddar or some
shit, man. -There you go.
-But I passed on that, man.
Look, I wanted that Fast
and the Furious soundtrack,
but, uh, I ain't get it.
Then I found out that
your ass got it, though.
Yeah, yeah. I got it. Yeah.
I mean, most of these majors'
stuff, they don't...
They don't look out
for black folks like that.
They don't put us on like that.
There's only one spot
for niggas,
and I got to get it,
so you know how that go.
Yeah, but how you be
getting that shit, though?
My manager, Luke.
He hooks it all up, man.
He has all the connections
with all the major brands.
He really does his job
really well, man.
If you want to talk to anybody,
just holler at Luke. Yeah.
-Yeah. -Got some waters
for you guys. -Oh, thanks, bro.
-Yeah, of course.
-I appreciate it, man.
Yo, pull up the
"King of Diamonds" joint.
-All right.
I'm not sure.
Let me know
when you're sure, okay?
I'm not playing
with you today, okay?
It's me and Paper Boi, man.
Come on, man, come on.
-Don't waste our time, bro.
-I got you.
You-you got me.
How much we got, man?
Fifty thou?
Ha, $50,000 on me.
Who are you on the phone with?
I see you.
Why you ain't bring no girls?
-I was calling
my accountant, nigga. -Hey!
No, it's just,
it's fucking amaz...
It crashed again.
Hey, yo, Boogz, I'm gonna go
for a walk real quick,
all right, man?
Y'all should go home.
-Yeah, man.
I was on my way out anyway,
you know what I mean.
-Good luck with your track, bro.
-Thanks, man.
-Appreciate it. Yep.
-Stay woke.
I'm gonna just take this, man,
'cause it's, like, half full.
-Oh, yeah, I-I got it, man.
-Yep, you got this.
We got it, we got it.
If you break it down, hookah
kind of sounds like something
the tobacco industry
created for six-year-olds.
You know what I'm saying?
Like... fruit-flavored smoke.
You're not supposed to
breathe it in, you know that?
-Thank you.
-No, Grandpa.
-Now I really hate it.
I got to pat you down, bro.
Sure, yeah. All right.
You're good, you're good, bro.
$20 for dudes, bro.
All right. $20?
There, you have
a good night, man.
-Thanks.
-Picture ID.
See?
You're not gonna tell me
it's not cute.
I thought I'd see more
Middle Eastern people here.
It's kind of weird.
Thank you.
Okay, so, which flavor
do you like?
'Cause mint is good,
but you can mix them.
I'm not really a mint guy.
-I don't like how it feels
in my mouth. -Oh, my God.
Especially with smoke...
You have the palate
of a three-year-old.
Untrue. I...
Sir, did you just pay
with that $100 bill outside?
Uh... yeah?
Well, that $100 bill was fake.
-You need to come with us.
What do you mean?
That bill you used was fake.
Let's go.
Are you sure it was mine?
You're the only one
who's paid with a $100 bill.
-Let's just go.
-All right.
You see? Right there.
There's the watermark.
No, no. You did that.
I did that?
What do you...?
No, man-- just-just get another
hundred to compare it.
There are no other hundreds
in the bar.
Do you got one of those...
one of those pens
that you can mark it with?
Of course not.
How do you even know it's fake?
I know, okay?
Here. Try and rip it up.
What?
What are you talking about?
That makes no sense.
I'm not falling for your tricks.
You know what?
It's fine. Just...
Just give me the...
Give me the money back.
I-I'll leave.
Yeah, but you
already came inside.
You still need to pay.
Hurry up!
Oh, my fucking God.
Hey.
We all know
that the bill was real,
but the owner was tripping.
Sorry about that.
That was definitely racist.
Yeah, what the fuck?
This is supposed to be
a celebration, man.
Yeah, I know.
Let's just get some food.
No, no, no.
I know where we're going.
Where we gonna go?
I'm going somewhere
where people definitely know
how to treat someone with money.
Yeah. A'ight, a'ight.
A'ight, man. Bet.
Hey, man.
Earn headed to the strip club.
You want to go slap some butts?
Nah, but I'll watch.
Huh-- all right.
Get dressed, nigga.
Earn trying to stunt tonight.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
That reminds me.
I got this brand-new
all-white suit.
On a bitch.
I'm-a throw that on.
You really want to wear all
white to a strip club, nigga?
You're right.
Tracy, you coming?
Yeah.
I'm ready.
Yeah, that's funny,
you know that we don't...
-Goddamn!
-No.
-That thing clean.
What y'all do, rob a prom?
Paper Boi, Paper Boi!
Hey, Vanessa.
-Hi, Alfred.
Y'all niggas is drunk.
Do you like my big car?
I-I don't want
to respond to that.
-That's weird.
Thank you for shuttling
us black people to Onyx.
-No,
this shit's gonna be tight, man.
Y'all stunting tonight.
We stunting tonight. Yeah.
All right, let's go.
* I tell all my hos,
rake it up *
* Break it down, bag it up *
* Fuck it up, fuck it up,
fuck it up, fuck it up *
* Back it up, back it up,
back it up *
* Rake it up, rake it up,
rake it up... *
DJ:
Yo! Fix your grill pieces.
Big baller alert!
We got Paper Boi
in the building tonight, ladies.
Yeah, yeah, give it up
for my man right there.
He's got his crew
and a white girl on his arm.
Yeah, I'm talking to you,
Annie Hall.
Pink toe.
Let's get it popping.
Shorty's ass so fat on stage,
look like a birth defect.
Oh!
* I said I'm that nigga, bitch,
I already know it... *
If there's anything
I can get you, let me know.
-Mm-hmm. -Your table does come
with a bottle of your choice,
so let me know
what I can get you.
-Hennessy Black.
-Uh, actually,
Van doesn't drink that,
so tequila.
-Got you.
-You're right, you're right.
I mean, I'm gonna drink
whatever you get.
Sure thing.
Uh, actually, uh, do you have
change for a hundred?
They can help you
at the bar. Come on.
I'll be back.
All right, man, cool.
Don't get lost in all this ass!
("I Get the Bag"
by Gucci Mane playing)
:
* Ha *
* It's Gucci *
* It's Drop Top *
* Wizop *
-* Hoo *
-* Skrrt *
* Yo... *
Hey.
Yoo-hoo!
* I get the bag and flip it
and tumble it... *
Um, can you turn
this hundred into ones?
Sure thing, papi.
Uh, we take 20%
to change it out,
and there's a $200 minimum.
-Mm-hmm.
All right.
* They DM me *
* Drop the top
when it's cold... *
Thank you.
-Have fun, baby.
-DJ: Yo, coming to the stage,
we got Bankhead Barbie.
You know her, you love her.
* They say the dope
on fleek... *
DJ: Yo, man,
don't just look at her, tip her.
* Them niggas that flex in
the back don't say nothin'... *
Man, where you going, my man?
I said, "Tip her."
Yeah, you,
with that green jacket
and that wack-ass
Coca-Cola T-shirt.
* My bitch, she walk around
like she Kris Jenner *
* I used to break
and then enter *
* Then Takeoff run 'em
like the game of temple... *
Aw, come on, man,
you can do better than that.
You just took $200
out the ATM machine
from your PNC checking account.
Nigga!
-Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Coming to the stage,
we ain't seen her a long time.
She been on house arrest for
giving illegal butt injections,
give it up for Bankhead Barbie!
* Way above the ground *
* Way above the ground... *
You want a dance, sweetheart?
Uh, no. But you can dance
for my girl over there.
Okay.
Okay, honey, that'll be $20.
-That wasn't even three seconds.
You-you didn't even
make it over there.
-Well, it's for a song.
Uh, we still haven't gotten
our tequila.
Yeah, I was waiting
on you guys to pay for it.
But it comes with the table.
Yeah, it comes with the table,
so you have to buy one.
How much?
$200, love.
All right, um...
-Here.
-Okay.
I'll be back with the drinks.
You got any ones?
I want to give it
to the girl on stage.
EARN:
But she's so skinny, and she...
-she's not doing anything.
: I know.
But I feel bad for her.
She seems new, and, like,
all the other girls
are so pretty,
and she shouldn't have
to compete.
All right.
You got it.
Pity dance.
I've never heard of that.
ALFRED :
"She looks new."
Man, that's Minnie.
Looking new her hook.
Yeah, she's been looking new for
about damn ten years now, man.
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah, well...
it's working for her.
Hmm.
Hey, man.
Van told me about
that $100 bill shit.
Yeah, that shit was wack.
Yeah, well, you can't be going
out spending $100 bills, nigga.
Why not?
It's legal U.S. tender.
Look at you, man.
You don't look like
no damn dope boy.
I'd think that shit
was fake, too.
-You told me
the only thing I needed
-to run this city was money.
-Mm-mmm.
Money is an idea, man.
Look, there's a reason that a
white dude dressed just like you
can walk into a bank
and get a loan,
and you can't even spend
a $100 bill, man.
I mean, you need to start
acting like you're better
than other niggas, and then
they'll start treating you
-better than other niggas.
-DARIUS: Yeah, 'cause otherwise,
-you're just another nigga.
-Another nigga.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
Hey, look at Tracy ass
over there, man.
He's been telling these hos
all night that he's my manager.
Yo, man. We should hire her, yo.
Hey!
-There it is!
I don't even know why I'm here.
This place has been
finessing me all night.
ALFRED:
Duh, nigga.
It's a strip club.
That's what it's for.
Yep. It ain't like
you're supposed to be
out here saving money.
ALFRED :
Yeah, ain't saving no money
-at no strip club.
-Yeah.
Nigga.
You okay?
Nah, I had fun.
VAN:
What is going on?
Yeah, Michael Vick out here
racing people.
He taking bets, too.
Yeah, boy, yeah.
Is he... is he doing okay?
Oh, he fine.
It's just a good hustle.
Yeah. Drunk people
just want to race him.
This his sixth race
in the ten minutes
I've been standing here.
-That boy's good.
Anybody?
MAN:
Three-to-one odds.
It's fair.
I kind of want to see this.
I'll do it.
No, what, wait...
what are you doing?
Sometimes you just got
to stunt on people.
And also, I haven't run
six races in ten minutes.
Should be good.
Let's make this quick.
HAT MAN:
Oh, shit.
DJ: All right, all right, all
right, fellas, fellas, fellas.
You know how we do it.
Let's get it going,
let's get it going.
A'ight?
On your mark.
Get set.
Go!
It's Michael Vick.
* We some marsupial *
* Superstars *
* I want the top,
who you fooling, yeah *
* I want a bitch
with big booty, yah *
* A-ya-ya-ya-ya, ooh *
* Bitch screaming
like a Indian *
* I want to fuck a amphibian *
* I keep a "K" like Sicilian *
* You can't suck dick,
you too pretty, huh *
* Diamonds straight
out of the freezer *
* I got more sauce
than a pizza *
* You ain't got to be
shy, girl *
* Swag make a bitch toot it up *
* Makin' dumb bread
'cause I'm shittin' on 'em *
* Gettin' dumb head,
stupid on 'em *
* Yellow diamond like
"Who pissed on me?" *
* Couple hittas
with them dicks on 'em *
* She too wet, wet,
let me fish on it *
* Break the bed legs,
now we on the floor *
* Put my cinnamon
in her Apple Jacks *
* I'm vegan,
throw that apple back *
* Apple back, ooh *
* Almost gave me
a asthma attack *
* Baby, let me freak you up,
down, up, down. *
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH